<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\XSL\topic.xsl"?>

<topic name="FindBrowser" type="method">
	<title>
		Open Twebst Library | Documentation - FindBrowser Method
	</title>

	<description>
		Connects a web automation Browser to an existing instance of <i>Internet Explorer</i> object ( <a target="_blank" href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/aa752127(VS.85).aspx">IWebBrowser2</a> ) that verifies a list of <reference href="SearchCondition.htm">Search Conditions</reference>.
	</description>

	<apply>
		<apply_item>Core</apply_item>
	</apply>

	<call>
		var b = coreObj.FindBrowser(Search conditions);
	</call>

	<arguments>
		<arg_summary>
			This method accepts a variable number of <reference href="SearchCondition.htm">Search Condition</reference> arguments.
			The following attributes are accepted in search conditions:
		</arg_summary>

		<arg><code>TITLE</code> condition on the title of the browser window</arg>
		<arg><code>URL</code> condition on the url of the web page</arg>
		<arg><code>APP</code> the name of the application hosting the <i>Internet Explorer</i> web control</arg>
	</arguments>

	<remarks>
		The method returns a web automation Browser object that matches the search condition arguments and gets programmatic control over the <a target="_blank" href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/aa752127(VS.85).aspx">IWebBrowser2</a> underlying IE native object.
		If no browser verifies the search conditions, then <i>null</i> is returned.<br/>
		In case of an error the method throws a web macro exception and the lastError property of the core object is set as follows:
		<ul>
			<li>INVALID_ARG_ERROR: if invalid parameters are provided</li>
			<li>FAIL_ERROR: in case of anohter error.</li>
		</ul>
		<br/>
		The time allocated for search is specified by the searchTimeout property.<br/>
		<i>APP</i> attribute is case insensitive. The default value is <i>iexplore.exe</i> and * stands for any application (including IE).
		This IE automation method works for all <i>Internet Explorer</i> versions: <i>IE6</i>, <i>IE7</i>, <i>IE8</i>, <i>IE9</i> and with <i>IE protected mode</i> on <i>Windows XP</i>, <i>Vista</i> and <i>Win7</i>.
	</remarks>

	<example>
		<jscode>
var coreObj = new ActiveXObject("OpenTwebst.Core");
var browser = coreObj.FindBrowser("URL=http://www.codecentrix.com/");

// If the browser is found then close it.
if (browser != null)
{
	browser.Close();
}
		</jscode>
	</example>

	<seealso>
		<seealso_item>Core</seealso_item>
		<seealso_item>Browser</seealso_item>
		<seealso_item>foregroundBrowser</seealso_item>
		<seealso_item>searchTimeout</seealso_item>
	</seealso>
</topic>
